when working with Word documents the may
be occasions where you need to change a
specific word or words within a document
if the document there's only one page
long that can be quite straightforward
and you can just go through and replace
each word manually however when working
with large documents it may be a case
that this is unrealistic and
time-consuming within word there is a
feature called find and replace which
will allow you to search for specific
words and then replace them with another
word in this example letter that I have
on the screen I'm going to find the word
information and replace that with the
word theatre I know there are several
instances of the word information so to
access the Feiner replace tool I simply
go to the edit menu button scroll down
to select find and then select replace
this brings up the find arias dialog box
so the word I'm looking for is
information and it will highlight every
instance of the word information and I'm
gonna change that with theatre so once
I'm happy if I select replace all that
will automatically replace every
instance of the word information with
the word theater